http://www.xtremegamesonline.com/policies

Store Categories
Please wait while we retrieve your cart.
Nintendo 64
- (N64)
Promo - Token
Promo - Unique & Misc.
Duel Decks: Elves vs Inventors
We Buy All Bulk!!!
Ultra Pro Satin Tower Deck Box
Ultimate Guard Deck Box -100 ct.
Store Hours
Central Time (US & Canada)
Monday - CLOSEDTuesday - 12:00 PM - 6:00 PMWednesday - 12:00 PM - 6:00 PMThursday - 12:00 PM - 6:00 PMFriday - 12:00 PM - 6:00 PMSaturday - 12:00 PM - 4:00 PMSunday - 12:00 PM - 4:00 PM
Policies
Purchasing and Shipping Policies
We have been having very high incidences of fraudulent orders.  That being said we no longer can Drop ship orders without verification. (send orders to different address than billing)  This policy does not include our military orders. We are sorry for the inconvience this may cause, but we need to protect all credit card holders against fraud.
Xtremegamesonline reserves the right to cancel any order outright or limit the quantity of part of an order at any time for any reason without prior notification. You will be immediately notified of the reasons your order was canceled, and any payment you made will be refunded immediately.
It has come to our attention, that some of the "Large" Internet dealers are watching smaller shop's inventory lists, and buying us out of potential "hot" cards, then raising prices.  We at Xtreme Games are in business for our customers/players to make decks, not to supply large dealers with inventory, for price fixing.  Because of this practice, if you wish to place an order for more that 8 of any 1 card in Magic the Gathering and 6 of any 1 card in Yugioh, you will need Admin approval prior to making your order.  Please email:  sales@xtremegamesonline.com  and we will review your order.  If you are an Internet dealer expect your order to be canceled.
Again this only to protect our customers/players....Sorry for any inconvenience
Sincerely,
Xtreme Games
International Customers
We are unable to shipped sealed Wizards Products Oversea's. We don't make the rules, We just follow them. We advise that any order over $100 dollars should have insurance Purchased and use a shipping service that you can Track to your doorstep.
ALL CUSTOMERS:
USPS: If you chose USPS as your shipping option please be aware that we do NOT guarantee the arrival of your package, if you do not choose some sort of tracking. About 1 in 5,000 packages are lost by the United States Postal Service, and many more packages experience delays in delivery for whatever reason. We do however 100% guarantee that each order is packaged and shipped promptly.
In Store Pick up
For Local Customers, we offer in store pick ups.
We need a minimum of 24 hours from when your order was placed to make sure it is pulled and available for pick up.  We do have a same day pick up option at additional cost.
All orders made this way need to be picked up within 5 days, unless you contact us and receive a responce agreeing to the delay.
Odrers not picked up will be canceled,and charged a 15% restocking fee.
Return PolicyYou may return most new, unopened items sold and fulfilled by XtremeGamesOnline.com within 30 days of delivery for a full refund, minus a small restocking fee. We'll also pay the return shipping costs and wave all fees if the return is a result of our error (you received an incorrect or defective item, etc.). RefundsRefunds are requested after we receive and process your return. You should expect to receive your refund within four weeks of giving your package to the return shipper, however, in many cases you will receive a refund more quickly. This time period includes the transit time for us to receive your return from the shipper (5 to 10 business days), the time it takes us to process your return once we receive it (3 to 5 business days), and the time it takes your bank to process our refund request (see below for specific guidelines). We'll notify you via e-mail of your refund once we've received and processed the returned item.
Out of Stock
Occasionally our inventory is incorrect and we are out of stock of an item, when this happens we will notify you through the email you provided as soon as the discrepancy is revealed. We will also credit your store credit account for that balance immediately. As always you may request that the balance be refunded to you through the payment method you used to pay us. (i.e. we would send the refund to your paypal account if you paid for your order through paypal)
If you pay by:
Your refund will go to:
... time until return is processed:
Credit Card
Credit Card
3-5 business days
Bank Account
Bank Account
Up to 10 business days
Check OR
Money Order
Store Credit Balance(to request a check,email us)
1 business day
Your PrivacyXtremeGamesOnline is committed to protecting your privacy. We only use the information we collect about you to process orders and to provide support and upgrades for our products. Please read on for more details about our privacy policy. What information do we collect? How do we use it?When you order, we need to know your name, e-mail address, mailing address, credit card number, and expiration date. This allows us to process and fulfill your order and to notify you of your order status. When you enter a contest or other promotional feature, we may ask for your name, address, and e-mail address so we can administer the contest and notify winners.
How does XtremeGamesOnline protect customer information?We use a Secure Server for collecting personal and credit card information. The secure server layer (SSL) encrypts (scrambles) all of the information you enter before it is transmitted over the Internet and sent to us. Furthermore, all of the customer data we collect is protected against unauthorized access. What about "cookies"?"Cookies" are small pieces of information that are stored by your browser on your computer's hard drive. We do not use cookies to collect or store any information about visitors or customers.Will XtremeGamesOnline disclose the information it collects to outside parties?XtremeGamesOnline does not sell, trade, or rent your personal information to others. XtremeGamesOnline may provide aggregate statistics about our customers, sales, traffic patterns, and related site information to reputable third-party vendors, but these statistics will not include personally identifying information.XtremeGamesOnline may release account information when we believe, in good faith, that such release is reasonably necessary to (i) comply with law, (ii) enforce or apply the terms of any of our user agreements or (iii) protect the rights, property or safety of XtremeGamesOnline, our users, or others. In SummaryXtremeGamesOnline is committed to protecting your privacy. We use the information we collect on the site to make shopping at XtremeGamesOnline.com as simple as possible and to enhance your overall shopping experience. We do not sell, trade, or rent your personal information to others.Your ConsentBy using our Web site, you consent to the collection and use of this information by XtremeGamesOnline, Inc. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it.XtremeGamesOnline also provides links to affiliated sites. The privacy policies of these linked sites are the responsibility of the linked site and XtremeGamesOnline has no control or influence over their policies. Please check the policies of each site you visit for specific information. XtremeGamesOnline cannot be held liable for damage or misdoings of other sites linked or otherwise.
By useing Xtremegameonline you agree to the terms and conditions set forth on our policy page
XtremeGamesOnline reserves the right to modify the policies outlined above at its sole discretion, which may become effective immediately and without notice.
Questions and FeedbackIf you have any questions or feedback related to our Policies, please email us at Sales@XtremeGamesonline.comThank you for shopping at XtremeGamesOnline.com!
